One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Cross this endless sea with me and search for
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please, following
the footprints of those who pursue their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we put our minds together,
we'll get through it
always
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Keep chasing, keep chasing
the compass that leads to our dreams
always points straight ahead
We can't stop here
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can take hold of tomorrow
Keep chasing, keep chasing
everything we see in the moment,
we should record it all
in the blank slates of our minds
Rob Lucci
Th-They're here! The bombardment has started!
Watch out!
Run!
Get us out of here!
I know!
The buster call has begun!
Our targets are Straw Hat Luffy
and his crew of about sixty pirates!
However, due to a private
agreement with Admiral Aokiji,
the criminal Nico Robin—last seen on
the Bridge of Hesitation—is not a target.
There's no need to assess the current situation!
Completely destroy the Judicial Island, Enies Lobby!
All battleships, take your positions!
I repeat. Our targets are Straw Hat Luffy
and his crew of about sixty pirates!
Completely destroy Enies Lobby!
Ah... H-Hey!
Hey, look, you guys! Don't run!
See? The battleships aren't attacking the bridge!
That's because I'm here!
That's right. My old man said the same thing.
He was the only one to avoid
the indiscriminate cannon fire!
However, the bridge with the criminal Nico Robin is not a target for now.
Hey! Look at this! This bridge is safe!
It's because I'm the chief of CP9!
What a crazy sight.
Hm? Hey, what's wrong?
I can't stop trembling.
Let's hurry, you guys! Be quick!
Stop bossing us around, you jerk!
If I may say one more thing,
this is aggravating my wounds.
Could you carry me a little more gently?
Don't ask too much!
Besides, you're contradicting yourself.
It's no exaggeration to say...
that I paid for the glory
of my actions with my entire body!
Ahh! All my ribs are broken! All six of them!
There are more than that, so don't worry.
Seriously, you're such a pain!
By the way, would you like to know
the secret of my new weapon, Kabuto?
I shall explain it to you. Kabuto, Sogeking's weapon, is-
– Ta-da!
– Shut up, you jerk! Or we'll make you run!
Please! Spare me! My ribs
are broken! A-All ten of them.
– There are more than that.
– What?
Then 20... 30?
How about 100?!
There are more than that!
No way that's true!
What's that?
Water!
What the heck is going on?!
Why is there water?! What?!
Why?! We have no way out!
Help!
I don't care whether anyone's in the corridor or not.
No one can get here now.
You bastard!
Soon this room will be underwater.
This room is above sea level.
The water won't reach here.
You can hear the sounds of the
battleships' cannon fire, right?
What happened to your crew?
What happened to Nico Robin?
You must be worried.
If you wanna go rescue them, go right ahead.
I won't let you out of my sight.
No matter what they're going through
right now, they'll survive for sure!
But if I let you get away now,
you'll go kill my friends!
I won't let you out of my sight!
The bombardment has begun.
By the way, I can hear a strange sound up ahead.
Shut your mouth!
Nooo!
Grandma! What's going on?!
Who cares?! Hurry up and run!
You make a pretty good boss.
I wish an idiot I know could hear you.
But I wonder, do you have the ability to back up your decision?
The result will be the same if you die!
Hey! Capture Nico Robin already!
Once this is all over, I'll be the world's hero!
The buster call sounds like a gun salute for me!
Razor!
Finger Pistol!
Tempest Kick: Leopard Tail!
Can you really defeat me?!
I can't protect anyone unless I win!
Rubber Rubber...
Rifle!
Iron Body: Fruitless Shrub.
Razor!
I salute you for having the guts to pick
a fight with the World Government.
Rubber Rubber Pistol!
Flying Finger Pistol:
Sting!
Triple Sting!
Flying Finger Pistol:
Fire Sting!
I thought I'd met a man with some backbone. How disappointing.
So you did run out of strength from your doping earlier?
If it's backbone you want, I'll show you...
another tactic!
Gear Third!
Bone Balloon!
Bone?
The power moves from one bone to another.
Take a look! My left arm is...
the arm of a giant!
If it's all show, don't even bother!
Rubber Rubber...
Iron Body!
Gigant Pistol!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
I feel like I'm about to pass out.
I can't fall into the sea like this!
Oops!
What was that?
Hurry and help the injured!
Who are you?!
– A beast?!
– No, he has an ability!
I landed on the deck of a battleship.
That was close.
He flew from the bridge.
Is he a pirate?
I saw a huge hand, too!
Stop! Stop! I said stop!
It's dangerous up ahead!
Water is rushing towards us!
C-Can't you guys hear the sound of water?!
Listen, if the water flows into
an underground passage like this,
we'll have no choice but to drown.
Zoro-kun, can't you hear the sound of water?!
Hmm, I agree that something doesn't feel right.
Then let's stop already!
There's no other way. We have to keep going!
I knew it!
Water is about to overwhelm Nami and the others!
Ah! Pirate guys!
Guys! Do something about this water!
Do something?! What're we supposed to do?!
See, I told you! This passage is
gonna be flooded with water!
N-Nami-san...
is rushing into my arms!
How optimistic!
This is bad! We're gonna be trapped in here!
I can't cut it! It's not iron or stone?!
This is an undersea passage.
It must be made of some damn thick steel
that can bear the water pressure!
Then there's nowhere to run!
Ahh! It's here!
It isn't safe here! We're gonna die!
Hurry!
We're doomed! The sea train won't start!
Where's the engineer?!
Let's get outta here! Come on!
Vice Admiral!
What do we do about capturing
Nico Robin on the Bridge of Hesitation?!
– Leave her alone.
– But...
As long as that man is on this island,
with the mission of escorting Nico Robin,
we don't have to get involved.
We'll just burn down everything but the Bridge of Hesitation.
Yes, sir!
Vice Admiral,
is the man you mentioned Rob Lucci of CP9?
As we suspected, he has a devil fruit ability!
Who the hell are you?!
We're asking who you are! Answer us!
Stand down, you idiots!
Captain?!
Put down your guns!
Who do you think you're talking to?!
He is Rob Lucci of CP9!
R-Rob Lucci-san!
What?! That's...
We're sorry! Please spare us!
Keep your mouths shut. Your whining is grating.
I've heard a lot about Rob Lucci,
but is he really that good?
It was fifteen years ago...
In one kingdom,
pirates captured some 500 soldiers.
In exchange for the hostages' lives,
the pirate captain demanded the throne.
The World Government sent a boy to the kingdom,
as it was on the verge of surrender,
due to its concern for the hostages.
A-A child?
Dammit! That blasted World
Government! How insulting!
Shave!
Tempest Kick!
He infiltrated the pirates' hideout...
and killed all 500 of the kingdom's soldiers on the spot.
He k-killed all of them?
That can't be! How could he be forgiven for that?!
Even if it's the World Government...
Even if it's for justice...
P-Pardon me!
Justice
Listen up. Justice isn't all warm and fuzzy!
None of you forget it!
Yes, sir!
The pirates were so enraged that they rained fire upon the boy,
who was standing on the pile of bodies with his back turned.
But the boy rose from the flames, killed the pirate captain,
and single-handedly put the whole affair to rest.
Wh-What the hell is this?!
How dare you kill our valuable hostages?!
They committed a crime,
so I executed them in the name of justice.
A crime?
As soldiers of the kingdom, being weak is a crime.
Guys! Take him down!
H-How could he have survived that?!
Shave!
Finger Pistol.
Captain!
H-He's a monster!
Help!
The boy with several cannonball scars on his back...
was a CP9 intelligence agent at the age of 13.
Some call him the most powerful and ruthless mass killing machine...
in the history of CP9 and its mission of covert justice.
It's unreal that he was capable of
all that when he was only 13.
That's precisely why all we have to do is carry out our duty.
Rubber Rubber...
Rocket!
What is it this time?!
Something came out!
That's Straw Hat Luffy,
whose bounty is 100 million belly!
I didn't think he'd be that fat.
There you are! Pigeon guy!
Shoot him down!
That won't work! The Bone Balloon is tough!
Rubber Rubber Gigant Axe!
Ahhh!
What the hell?! Is it a giant?!
Rubber Rubber Gigant Whip!
Whoa! Watch out!
The masts snapped!
They're collapsing!
The fight between those two is insane!
Finger Pistol: Sting!
It seems that as you grow more powerful, you become slower.
Tempest Kick: Victory Bird!
He cracked the iron hull!
This ship won't last long!
That was close. I almost got split in two.
Did you see that, Cutty Flam?!
It's all over for you guys!
Or rather, it was all over from the start!
It's a bit early to say that
when the fight isn't over yet!
Lucci is the one fighting Straw Hat.
He's the strongest man in the history of CP9!
You might've managed to get rid of the others somehow,
but Lucci's another story entirely!
Once Straw Hat's taken care of,
you're next, Cutty Flam!
I'm counting on you, Straw Hat!
What's going on? Give me a report.
Yes, sir, Vice Admiral!
We heard that Straw Hat Luffy and
Rob Lucci of CP9 are currently fighting.
As a result, battleship No. 4 is in bad shape!
Rob Lucci isn't gonna die.
All gunners, target battleship No. 4!
Prepare all guns for a volley in five seconds!
What?! Vice Admiral, you must be kidding.
One thousand of our men are onboard!
A moment's indecision can allow
vicious criminals to slip away.
Can you protect our future from them?
Fire!